areavibes.com 2018-10-12

# Privacy Policy - AreaVibes

AreaVibes Inc. recognizes that the privacy of your personal information is important. Personal information is collected by this website with your knowledge and consent. Personal information is collected when you register a member account or a business account. During registration you may be asked to submit personal details such as your first name, last name, gender, location, e-mail address as well as other optional information. By submitting the information through these forms, you agree to the storage of this information by AreaVibes Inc.

AreaVibes Inc. will not sell or disclose your personal information to third parties. However, in the following instances we reserve the right to disclose this information: 

  * While enforcing the AreaVibes Inc. terms of use
  * For any reason required by law
  * To protect other users of the website
  * To protect the general safety and rights of the public

AreaVibes Inc. may also send you information if you have chosen to receive AreaVibes Inc. news or daily updates during the registration process. You may opt out of receiving this information at any time.

AreaVibes Inc. may also collect information about your computer and your browsing patterns during your visit to the website. This information includes, but is not limited to, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, time of visit and pages visited. AreaVibes Inc. may also use "cookies" to collect data and information. A cookie, also known as web cookie, browser cookie and HTTP cookie, is a piece of text that is stored on your web browser. AreaVibes Inc. will use cookies for a variety of purposes, including, but not limited to: authenticating usernames and passwords, site preferences, search preferences as well as other uses. This information allows us to maintain and enhance your overall experience with AreaVibes Inc.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve the ads displayed on our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email or phone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

AreaVibes Inc. may display information and links from advertisers, affiliates and other partners. We expect this information to be displayed in a manor alike to our terms of use and privacy policy. However, third parties, may abide by their own terms of use and privacy policy. AreaVibes Inc. is not affiliated with these third parties and is not responsible for the content or actions of these third parties.

AreaVibes Inc. may use Google site stats to track conversions and clicks from Google Adwords. This is a small piece of code that is attached to our pages to determine when a page has been visited.

AreaVibes Inc. reserves the right to change or update this privacy policy at any time, without notice. Please revisit this privacy policy periodically to ensure you are aware of any such changes. AreaVibes Inc. may, at any time, restrict your access to this website. If you continue use of this website, then by default you agree to the privacy policy.
